[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the director of the hit movie The Shawshank Redemption?", "correct_answer": "Frank Darabont", "incorrect_answers": ["Ron Howard", "Rob Reiner", "Shimon  Bentzvi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following was action star Bruce Lee able to do?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Do push-ups supporting himself on the thumb and index finger of one hand", "Throw rice into the air and catch the grains in midair with chopsticks", "Thrust his fingers through an unopened soft drink can made from thick steel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is a lamprey?", "correct_answer": "fish", "incorrect_answers": ["worm", "insect", "amphibian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the smallest ocean?", "correct_answer": "The Arctic Ocean", "incorrect_answers": ["The Atlantic Ocean", "The Indian Ocean", "The Southern Ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 2001 Maniacs, at the BBQ, Anderson and the mayor fight. What happens when Anderson lifts the mayors eye patch?", "correct_answer": "Maggots falls from his eye socket.", "incorrect_answers": ["There is nothing wrong with the covered eye.", "A bullet falls from his eye socket.", "His eye falls out."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the special power of agent Juarez from the 3-D action comedy G-Force?", "correct_answer": "Martial arts", "incorrect_answers": ["High-tech surveillance", "Cyber intelligence", "Weapons and transportation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the active volcano situated in Skamania County, Washington, USA, 50 miles (80 km) northeast of Portland, Oregon?", "correct_answer": "Mount St. Helens", "incorrect_answers": ["Mount St. Augustus", "Mount St. Paul", "Mount St. Georges"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Oklahoma city saw a race riot that triggered a fire in 1921?", "correct_answer": "Tulsa", "incorrect_answers": ["Enid", "Ada", "Oklahoma City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is said to have occurred at Cenacle?", "correct_answer": "The Last Supper", "incorrect_answers": ["The assassination of  Arch Duke Francis Ferdinand", "The building of the Parthenon", "The assassination of Julius Caesar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Moggridge is commonly credited with the creation of the first true laptop computer, in this year.", "correct_answer": "1979", "incorrect_answers": ["1984", "1963", "1634"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is a water soluble vitamin also known as riboflavin?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B2", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin C", "Vitamin A", "Vitamin E"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the deepest lake in the world?", "correct_answer": "Baikal", "incorrect_answers": ["Caspian Sea", "Issyk-Kul", "Tanganyika"]}]